Hi, I'm Anna Klibanov

gobanana.ca / anna.klibanov@gmail.com

Over the last 15 years, I've worked across diverse industries designing and building software. My most scaled work was at Edsby, an education platform servicing over 215 million users worldwide and winning more than 70 awards. My passion lies in crafting functional and usercentric products, where I meticulously consider both high-level perspectives and minute details. My skill set, spanning creative, practical, and technical domains, gives me a unique approach to product design and management. I'm creative, adaptive, and love to learn. I am motivated by a challenge and love the reward of overcoming obstacles.

Work Experience

June 2010- Freelance Designer
Present GoBanana Design

Extensive experience working with clients across all industries and media. Worked with clients on small projects like single-page websites as well as large-scale projects including print and digital materials from concept to full execution installations.

Oct 2022- Senior UX/UI Designer

Sep 2023 ActiveState

Managed a design team to deliver solutions that offered an exceptional user experience while meeting business requirements. Employed key performance indicators (KPIs) and Net Promoter Score (NPS) metrics to measure the success of the designs, ensuring they aligned with company goals. Worked closely with the engineering team on the effective execution of the designs. Participated and assisted in product management and planning to achieve strategic objectives.

Sep 2020- Scrum Master

July 2022 Edsby

Led a 20+ person engineering team in Agile development. Facilitated relationships with the Product Owner, business team, customer needs, and other stakeholders to ensure a clear and seamless product development process.

April 2011-July 2022 Senior UX/UI Designer / Product Designer / Front-End Developer

Edsby

Designed UI mockups for the software to create an easy and pleasant user experience; taking into account market research, user testing, customer needs, and business requirements. Collaborated with the engineering team to ensure implementation of designs and seamless product deployment.

2010-2011

Graphic and Web Designer / Front-End Web Developer

Ingle International

Designed and developed websites for clients, created mockups for intuitive user interfaces for web applications, and worked closely with programmers to achieve optimal functionality. Created other materials for the company and its clients, such as interactive flash presentations and print materials.

2008-2011

Web Designer and Technician

York University

Maintained the web sites for the Fine Arts Computing department and Visual Resources Centre. Assisted faculty with technical problems, and troubleshot more complicated issues to relay the information to the next level of support.

Skills

- Product design
- UX/UI design
- User research and testing
- Wireframing and prototyping
- Web development
- Branding
- · Project management
- Team leadership

- Verbal, written, and interpersonal communication
- Adobe Creative Suite
- Figma
- MS Visual Studio
- HTML/CSS
- Javascript

Education

2020 Certified ScrumMaster (CSM)

Scrum Alliance

2006-2010 Bachelor of Design (Honours)

York University/Sheridan College